https://www.fiveseasonshealing.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentWe are now open for in-person acupuncture and virtual consultations. book now Privacy PolicyFive Seasons Healing Acupuncture Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.fiveseasonshealing.com (the “Site”).Personal Information We CollectWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”We collect Device Information using the following technologies:– “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.– “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.– “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site. Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.” When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.How do we use your Personal Information?We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to: Communicate with you; Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services. We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).Sharing Your Personal Information We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.Behavioral AdvertisingAs described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work. You can opt out of targeted advertising by: FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads GOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous BING – https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-adsAdditionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.Do Not TrackPlease note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.Your RightsIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below. Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.Data RetentionWhen you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.ChangesWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.Contact UsFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at hello@fiveseasonshealing.com or by mail using the details provided below: 135 West 29th Street, Suite 1103, New York, NY, 10001, United States Start Your Wellness Journey TodayWe offer convenient online booking, weekday and weekend appointments, and a complimentary ten minute phone consult to see if we are right for you.
Call Now
Book Appointment
Directions
Get in Touch
Quick LinksFertilityWomen’s HealthPregnancy & Maternal HealthOther ConditionsFirst VisitInsuranceFAQ
MenuFertilityWomen’s HealthPregnancy & Maternal HealthOther ConditionsFirst VisitInsuranceFAQ Why Five Seasons?According to Chinese medicine philosophy, each year is divided into five seasons—spring, summer, late summer, autumn, and winter–each linked to a unique elemental energy. When we eat peas in the spring and pumpkin in the fall, or play under the sun in the summer and cozy up to a fire in the winter, we are attuned to the earth’s natural rhythms. Just as different seasons call for distinct forms of care, so do the different seasons of our lives.
Call: 917-538-5755
Email: hello@fiveseasonshealing.com
Visit: NoMad | The Haymarket Building, 135 West 29th St., Suite 1103, New York, NY 10001 Start Your Wellness Journey TodayWe offer convenient online booking, weekday and weekend appointments, and a complimentary ten minute phone consult to see if we are right for you.
Call Now
Book Appointment
Directions
Why Five Seasons?According to Chinese medicine philosophy, each year is divided into five seasons—spring, summer, late summer, autumn, and winter–each linked to a unique elemental energy. When we eat peas in the spring and pumpkin in the fall, or play under the sun in the summer and cozy up to a fire in the winter, we are attuned to the earth’s natural rhythms. Just as different seasons call for distinct forms of care, so do the different seasons of our lives.Quick LinksFertilityWomen’s HealthPregnancy & Maternal HealthOther ConditionsFirst VisitInsuranceFAQ
MenuFertilityWomen’s HealthPregnancy & Maternal HealthOther ConditionsFirst VisitInsuranceFAQ
Call: 917-538-5755
Email: hello@fiveseasonshealing.com
Visit: NoMad | The Haymarket Building, 135 West 29th St., Suite 1103, New York, NY 10001
Stay ConnectedSign up to receive our wellness newsletter which we publish a few times a year.
Sign up
